<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashley Getty</title>
    <description>Ashley Getty</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 20:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 20:09:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Handbell</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In late 2018, I had the pleasure of working with the Hershey Handbell Ensemble on a freelance project to design a new logo for the PA-based organization. I created a variety of options that incorporated both a modern and a vintage feel. In the end, the client preferred the more modern, circular design. I also created a few abbreviated logo options to be used for embroidery and other smaller, less detailed items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Initial concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/handbell-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Chosen option.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/handbell-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Alternate logo designs; chosen design shown in physical context.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/handbell-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/handbell</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/handbell</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Logos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Below are some of my favorite logos concepts that I created for clients of Worboys Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/logos</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/logos</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Branded Bicycle</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;St Paul Collection, a luxury apartment community located in Denver’s Cherry Creek neighborhood, came to Worboys Design with the unique idea of using branded bicycles as advertising pieces that could be placed around Cherry Creek. Worboys Design had never worked on a project quite like this before, and I had the opportunity to be the sole designer on the project. I began by finding a bike frame that could effectively emulate a luxurious, upscale look &amp;amp; feel. I then used Photoshop to mock up a design that represented the St Paul brand. I found &amp;amp; sourced a local bike vendor to do all the production work for the project - from the paint job &amp;amp; leather details the custom chain guard, signage panel, &amp;amp; crate. The finished product turned out better than my team &amp;amp; I could have imagined, and we are excited to see these bikes pop up in the Cherry Creek neighborhood. Many thanks to Ian at &lt;a href=&quot;http://whiterhinocustoms.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;White Rhino Customs&lt;/a&gt; for his creativity and hard work to help bring this project to completion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/brandedbicycle-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Finished photos.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/brandedbicycle-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/branded-bicycle</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/branded-bicycle</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bantam</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The owner of Bantam Vintage Rentals was interested in a detailed, classic look for this design. I began by illustrating a hen, scanning and manipulating it into a usable digital format, and finally creating a simple but elegant logo that was centered around the illustration. Below are some examples of the logo used in various contexts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/bantam</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/bantam</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonderwood</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Wonderwood is a rustic lakeside lodge located in Grand Lake, Colorado. I had the pleasure of creating a logo &amp;amp; website for this beautiful alpine getaway. Once the logo design was chosen, I began designing the site. I created a design that allowed the photography of the lodge to speak for itself and create a perfect foundation for the rest of the site. Some of the website’s features include local attractions, an amenities list, photo gallery, and contact info page. I wrote all the site’s copy, and used my hand lettering skills to create a header for each interior page. I then built a responsive website using the Divi plugin on WordPress, which allows a high degree of design customization. To see the website in more detail, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://wonderwoodgrandlake.com&quot;&gt;wonderwoodgrandlake.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Logo concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/wonderwood-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Chosen design, shown in various contexts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/wonderwood-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Responsive site design.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/wonderwood-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wonderwood</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/wonderwood</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Invites</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two of my favorite types of design work are invitation suites and event collateral. I like to use hand lettering to add unique touches to the designs. When time allows, I also print the invitations using my Epson R2000 printer. It’s always gratifying to see a project through from start to finish in my own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I also created the place cards and many of the signs that were featured at my own wedding by hand.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/invites</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/invites</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dental</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most unique projects I worked on at Stoner Graphix was this mobile dentist’s office for Capital Blue Cross. Precision was key here, as the vehicle had many windows, doors, and extendable portions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the graphics appear to have been printed on a single piece of material, they were actually broken down to be printed and plotted on 3 different vinyl types. The solid navy blue (background) and bright blue (toothbrush handle) were cut from colored vinyl. Everything else (bristles, bubbles, &amp;amp; text) was digitally printed onto white vinyl, then laminated and plotted from cut paths I created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My involvement in the project included creating a kid-friendly, fun design that adhered to the brand standards of Capital Blue Cross, fitting that design to the supplied vehicle measurements, breaking down the graphics into print-friendly files, producing (printing, laminating, and plotting) all the vinyl, and supplying the production team with measurements for the install.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-3.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-4.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-5.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A closer look at the toothbrush design.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The screenshots below show some of the more noteworthy parts of the design process.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top:&lt;/strong&gt; The van mocked up in Illustrator and ready to be proofed to the client.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom:&lt;/strong&gt; A detailed look at one of the print files; the pink stroke indicates the path where the plotter blade would actually cut the vinyl. Complex bleed was added to each shape, taking into consideration characteristics such as transparencies, gradients, sharp angles, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dental</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dental</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hershey</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Hershey Company is one of Stoner Graphix’s major clients, and I had the pleasure of working on quite a few projects for them. I’ve selected this one in particular (done for the Target Corporation sales office in Minneapolis, MN) because it shows a variety of vinyl wall graphics, standoff-mounted panels, dimensional lettering, and frosted window vinyl.  In addition to this location, I’ve also worked on graphics for offices in Rhode Island, Illinois, Ohio, and their Corporate Headquarters in Hershey, Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I was the lead designer on this project, so my duties included laying out Hershey's branding patterns and imagery to fit specific wall sizes, breaking down all the graphics for print, printing the graphics on our large format printers, creating outsource files for the dimensional letters, and providing the installation team with measurements for the install. I've included photos of the finished work, as well as a few screenshots showing my specific roles throughout the project.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Standoff-mounted panels: For the graphics in the next two photos, each panel was printed in reverse on clear vinyl, laminated with opaque white vinyl, and applied to the reverse side of routed clear acrylic panels. Thus, the graphics are actually located on the back side of the panels, which makes them less susceptible to the usual wear and tear.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Etchmark Vinyl: The window/door graphics in the next two photos were plotted from a material called Etchmark. This gray, translucent vinyl allows for some privacy while still letting light shine through.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The screenshots below show some of the more noteworthy parts of the design process.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/hershey-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hershey&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Left:&lt;/strong&gt; In addition to the conference rooms, there were also nineteen offices that received wall graphics. This screen shows my master layout for all the rooms. I was given overall measurements/window placement for each room; then I picked a pattern that would complement each space. All graphics were broken into 50” wide strips so they could be printed on the large format printer.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Middle:&lt;/strong&gt; These graphics were sized for a conference room (see first two photos above). The “bumpout” is a characteristic that is fairly common for wall graphics; designs and measurements must always be precise so the final product fits the space correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Right:&lt;/strong&gt; This is the master layout for the etchmark window graphics. The graphics for each pane were plotted separately, and measurements were given for the installation team. Eight offices received these graphics.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/hershey</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/hershey</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lettering Illustration</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In my free time, I enjoy hand lettering &amp;amp; illustration. For lettering, I like to alternate between Tombow Fudenosuke brush pens and digital lettering with a stylus. Micron pens are typically my weapon of choice for illustration, and I tend to favor subject matter that is connected to nature. I enjoy digging deep into each illustration piece and including lots of detail, as I find it to be therapeutic and relaxing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/lettering-illustration-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;illustration&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lettering-illustration</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lettering-illustration</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
