<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashley Getty</title>
    <description>Ashley Getty</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 12:18:36 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 12:18:36 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Broadstone</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alliance Residential is one of Worboys Design’s largest clients, and we have partnered with them on multiple large-scale multifamily residential branding projects over the years. Broadstone Uptown is the most recent, with construction in full swing as of Spring 2019. This community will be located in the heart of Denver’s vibrant Uptown neighborhood - its interiors a fusion between two contrasting styles that both enhance and complement one another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the onset of the project, the client requested the creation of a splash page to serve as a point of contact for potential residents and a source of information regarding construction updates. Prior to this, one of my teammates at Worboys had created a mood board to serve as direction for the project’s overall look and feel. I used this as a starting point which guided the design aesthetic and color palette for the project. A feeling of modern luxury is conveyed in the design, with dueling dark &amp;amp; light sections as well as fine gold accents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The splash page is live and can be found here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.broadstoneuptown.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;broadstoneuptown.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;no-shadow&quot; src=&quot;../img/uptown-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Broadstone Uptown&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Below is the mood board which provided design direction for the splash page.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/uptown-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Broadstone Uptown&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/broadstone</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/broadstone</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forden</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The owner of Paige Forden Photography (Paige Kushner) came to Worboys Design looking for a rebrand that could accurately represent her work, process, &amp;amp; personality. Paige takes the time to get to know each and every one of her clients in order to build strong relationships with them, and wanted a brand identity that could portray that. This focus on connection plays a big role in Paige’s work - she is able to capture real, honest moments in the lives of children and families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I began the branding process by creating a mood board, based on some initial research as well as Paige’s overall vision for her new brand. Paige has a bold, edgy style that pairs well with her friendly and approachable demeanor. I wanted to make sure her new brand mirrored that.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Below is the finalized mood board. The soft, natural blush tones work to draw viewers in and make them feel at home while the high-contrast dark colored accents create a polished, refined, and fashionable look. Subtle sage and light grey tones soften up the overall color palette. Together, these colors create an identity that accurately portrays Paige’s passion of capturing pure, authentic moments in the lives of her clients.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/paigeforden-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Once the mood board was finalized, I proceeded to create logo design concepts that would later be presented to the client. I sat down with her to present the logo options and give her insight into the design choices behind each one.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/paigeforden-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In the end, the below concept was chosen.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/paigeforden-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/paigeforden-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/paigeforden-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/forden</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/forden</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vsv</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Vin Sur Vingt is a collection of authentic French Wine bars with locations throughout Manhattan, NYC - and a long-time client of Worboys Design. They came to us looking for a site refresh, as their previous site had been created quite a few years ago and was starting to feel outdated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the lead designer on this project, my role included project/account management, creation of new designs for the new website, and efficient communication with the developer during production. During the redesign, I also worked to improve the overall UX of Vin Sur Vingt’s website by revisiting the setup of the navigation, location info, and menus. Users will now easily be able to find exactly what they are looking for during their time visiting the site - whether it is a certain location’s menu/contact info, information on catering and private events, or simply to learn more about Vin Sur Vingt and its story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of April 2019, the site redesign is in the development stage, but page mockups can be found below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img class=&quot;no-shadow&quot; src=&quot;../img/vsv-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/vsv-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/vsv-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/vsv</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/vsv</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Handbell</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In late 2018, I had the pleasure of working with the Hershey Handbell Ensemble on a freelance project to design a new logo for the PA-based organization. I created a variety of options that incorporated both a modern and a vintage feel. In the end, the client preferred the more modern, circular design. I also created a few abbreviated logo options to be used for embroidery and other smaller, less detailed items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Initial concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/handbell-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Chosen option.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/handbell-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Alternate logo designs; chosen design shown in physical context.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/handbell-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;handbell&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/handbell</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/handbell</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Branded Bicycle</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;St Paul Collection, a luxury apartment community located in Denver’s Cherry Creek neighborhood, came to Worboys Design with the unique idea of using branded bicycles as advertising pieces that could be placed around Cherry Creek. Worboys Design had never worked on a project quite like this before, and I had the opportunity to be the sole designer on the project. I began by finding a bike frame that could effectively emulate a luxurious, upscale look &amp;amp; feel. I then used Photoshop to mock up a design that represented the St Paul brand. I found &amp;amp; sourced a local bike vendor to do all the production work for the project - from the paint job &amp;amp; leather details the custom chain guard, signage panel, &amp;amp; crate. The finished product turned out better than my team &amp;amp; I could have imagined, and we are excited to see these bikes pop up in the Cherry Creek neighborhood. Many thanks to Ian at &lt;a href=&quot;http://whiterhinocustoms.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;White Rhino Customs&lt;/a&gt; for his creativity and hard work to help bring this project to completion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/brandedbicycle-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;brandedbicycle&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Finished photos.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/brandedbicycle-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;brandedbicycle&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/branded-bicycle</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/branded-bicycle</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Logos</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Below are some of my favorite logo concepts that I created for clients of Worboys Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;logos&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;logos&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;logos&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/logos-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;logos&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/logos</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/logos</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bantam</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The owner of Bantam Vintage Rentals was interested in a detailed, classic look for this design. I began by illustrating a hen, scanning and manipulating it into a usable digital format, and finally creating a simple but elegant logo that was centered around the illustration. Below are some examples of the logo used in various contexts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/bantam-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bantam&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/bantam</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/bantam</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonderwood</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Wonderwood is a rustic lakeside lodge located in Grand Lake, Colorado. I had the pleasure of creating a logo &amp;amp; website for this beautiful alpine getaway. Once the logo design was chosen, I began designing the site. I created a design that allowed the photography of the lodge to speak for itself and create a perfect foundation for the rest of the site. Some of the website’s features include local attractions, an amenities list, photo gallery, and contact info page. I wrote all the site’s copy, and used my hand lettering skills to create a header for each interior page. I then built a responsive website using the Divi plugin on WordPress, which allows a high degree of design customization. To see the website in more detail, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://wonderwoodgrandlake.com&quot;&gt;wonderwoodgrandlake.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Logo concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/wonderwood-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wonderwood&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Chosen design, shown in various contexts.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/wonderwood-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wonderwood&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Responsive site design.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/wonderwood-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;wonderwood&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wonderwood</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/wonderwood</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Invites</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two of my favorite types of design work are invitation suites and event collateral. I like to use hand lettering to add unique touches to the designs. When time allows, I also print the invitations using my Epson R2000 printer. It’s always gratifying to see a project through from start to finish in my own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I also created the place cards and many of the signs that were featured at my own wedding by hand.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/invites-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;invites&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/invites</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/invites</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dental</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most unique projects I worked on at Stoner Graphix was this 40’ long mobile dentist’s office for local healthcare provider Capital Blue Cross. Precision was key here, as the vehicle had many windows, doors, and extendable portions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the graphics appear to have been printed on a single piece of material, they were actually broken down to be printed and plotted on 3 different vinyl types. The solid navy blue (background) and bright blue (toothbrush handle) were cut from colored vinyl. Everything else (bristles, bubbles, &amp;amp; text) was digitally printed onto white vinyl, then laminated and plotted from cut paths I created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My involvement in the project included creating a kid-friendly, fun design that adhered to the brand standards of Capital Blue Cross, fitting that design to the supplied vehicle measurements, breaking down the graphics into print-friendly files, producing (printing, laminating, and plotting) all the vinyl, and supplying the production team with measurements for the install.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A closer look at the toothbrush design.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The screenshots below show some of the more noteworthy parts of the design process.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;../img/dental-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;dental&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top:&lt;/strong&gt; The van mocked up in Illustrator and ready to be proofed to the client.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom:&lt;/strong&gt; A detailed look at one of the print files; the pink stroke indicates the path where the plotter blade would actually cut the vinyl. Complex bleed was added to each shape, taking into consideration characteristics such as transparencies, gradients, sharp angles, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dental</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dental</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
